MASHFIQ RAYHAN OVI BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (BSCSE)



Personal Details

- Mashfiq Rayhan Ovi
- 01764321053
- mashfa.rayhan.ovi@gmal.com
- Nirala RIA road na 1
 9100 Khulna
- 🔢 July 11th, 1997
- Khulna City
- **♂** Male
- Bangladeshi
- Single
- in linikedin.com/in/mashfiq -rayhan- 766959140

SKILLS

HTML5	••••
CSS3	••••
JavaScript	••••
React.JS	••••
Node.JS	••••
Express.JS	••••
Material-UI	••••

EDUCATION

JAN2015-MAY2022

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering (BSCSE) North South University. Dhaka

CSE Major Electives

- Internet and Web Technology
- Machine Learning
- Pattem Recognition and Neural Network

HSC

Govt. M. M. City College. Khulna Jun 2012 - May 2014

SSC

Khulna Zila School, Khulna Jan 2004 - Apr 2012

EMPLOYMENT

Software Engineer

Jan 2021 - Present GeekyCloud,Khulna CinePlex.live

Internship Engineer

Oct 2020 - Jan 2021

GeekyCloud,Khulna Admin Panel of CinePlex.live

Profile

Hello, I am Mashfiq Rayhan Ovi, I have Studied in Bachelor of Science(Bsc) in Computer Science and Engineering from North South University, Dhaka, Bangladesh. During my Bsc I have done different kinds of subject related projects like Database, Data Science and Pattern Recognition etc. I have Completed a NodeJS project During my Internship in GeekyCloud.net which is CinePlex.live Currently I am working on a Project of React - Full Stack Engineering - An Ecommerce site. "I'm an engineer with experience in building websites for small and medium sized businesses. Whether you're trying to win work, list your services or even create a whole website for your Business - I can help! * I'm experienced in HTML and CSS3, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, Express.js and Material-UI etc * I'll fully project manage your brief from start to finish. * Regular communication is really important to me, so let's keep in touch!" Let's build some good projects together.

Bootstrap Redux Python MySQL MongoDB Languages

English

INTEREST

- Machine learning
- Programming
- Traveling
- Learning Technologies
- Riding Bike & Stunt
- Pets
- Games

QUALITIES

- Technology Enthusiast
- Interpersonal skills
- Teamwork skills
- Leadership skills
- Attention to detail
- Management and organizational skills
- Willingness to learn
- Flexibility

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITES

JUN2012-DEC2014

Director

Ferocious Flash, Khulna

Ferocious Flash is an organization of Bikers and bike Stunts

Internships

Oct 2020 - Jan 2021

Internship Engineer

GeekyCloud,Khulna

Admin Panel of CinePlexlive

Major Courses

Internet and Web Technologies	2020
Machine Learning	2020
Pattern Recognition and Neural Network	2020

Certificates

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and	2022
Engineering (BSCSE)	
Higher Secondary School Certificate	2014
Secondary School Certificate	2012

Achievements

1st: RunnerUP - Math Olympiad (2006) Khulna Division

References

Mr. Farhad Hussain Munna GeekyCloud, Khulna 01714444441 fhmunna@gmail.com



GitHub

https://github.com/mashfiq-rayhan